export const Questions = [
  {
    prompt: "Are you a realistic person?",
    optionA: "Yes",
    optionB: "No",
    optionC: "Sometimes",
    optionD: "I don't know",
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    prompt: "What is your favourite food?",
    optionA: "Burger",
    optionB: "Soup",
    optionC: "Salads",
    optionD: "Chocolate",
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Do you have a high tolerance level?",
    optionA: "I don't know",
    optionB: "No",
    optionC: "Sometimes",
    optionD: "Yes",
    answer: "D",
  },
  {
    prompt: "How often do you cry?",
    optionA: "Every day",
    optionB: "Once a week",
    optionC: "Once a month",
    optionD: "Never",
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    prompt: "What is your favorite part of the day?",
    optionA: "Morning",
    optionB: "Afternoon",
    optionC: "Evening",
    optionD: "Night",
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    prompt: "How often do you get angry?",
    optionA: "Often",
    optionB: "Sometimes",
    optionC: "Rarely",
    optionD: "Never",
    answer: "D",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Do you have friends older than you?",
    optionA: "A few",
    optionB: "No",
    optionC: "Yes, many",
    optionD: "I don't know",
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Do you like to get up early in the morning?",
    optionA: "Yes",
    optionB: "No",
    optionC: "Sometimes",
    optionD: "I don't know",
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Do you care about your style?",
    optionA: "No",
    optionB: "Yes",
    optionC: "Sometimes",
    optionD: "A lot",
    answer: "B",
  },
  {
    prompt: "What would you do if you won the lottery?",
    optionA: "Buy a new car",
    optionB: "Party",
    optionC: "Add money to savings",
    optionD: "Buy a new house",
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    prompt: "What has the highest value to you?",
    optionA: "Fun",
    optionB: "Loyalty",
    optionC: "Happiness",
    optionD: "Discipline",
    answer: "B",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Have you ever gone through hard times?",
    optionA: "I don't know",
    optionB: "No",
    optionC: "Yes",
    optionD: "Maybe",
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Do you care about the environment?",
    optionA: "Yes",
    optionB: "No",
    optionC: "Sometimes",
    optionD: "I don't know",
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Do you want to live alone?",
    optionA: "Yes",
    optionB: "No",
    optionC: "Sometimes",
    optionD: "Never thought about it",
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    prompt: "How often do you miss a deadline?",
    optionA: "Always",
    optionB: "Sometimes",
    optionC: "Rarely",
    optionD: "Never miss",
    answer: "D",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Would you like to go on a trip abroad?",
    optionA: "Yes",
    optionB: "No",
    optionC: "In future",
    optionD: "I don't know",
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Are you very emotional?",
    optionA: "Yes",
    optionB: "No",
    optionC: "Sometimes",
    optionD: "I don't know",
    answer: "B",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Where would you like to live?",
    optionA: "In a city",
    optionB: "In a town",
    optionC: "City centre",
    optionD: "In the countryside",
    answer: "D",
  },
  {
    prompt: "How often do you sing?",
    optionA: "Often",
    optionB: "Rarely",
    optionC: "Sometimes",
    optionD: "Never",
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Do you want to grow up?",
    optionA: "Yes",
    optionB: "No",
    optionC: "Sometimes",
    optionD: "I don't know",
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Do you enjoy laughing at other people?",
    optionA: "Yes",
    optionB: "No",
    optionC: "Sometimes",
    optionD: "I don't know",
    answer: "B",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Do you enjoy reading books?",
    optionA: "Yes",
    optionB: "No",
    optionC: "Sometimes",
    optionD: "Rarely",
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Do you have a plan for the future?",
    optionA: "No",
    optionB: "Yes",
    optionC: "Maybe",
    optionD: "I don't know",
    answer: "B",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Your gender?",
    optionA: "Male",
    optionB: "Female",
    optionC: "Other",
    optionD: "Not prefer to tell",
    answer: "E",
  },
];
